[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Pandas are known to roar.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which fictional character had T-Negative blood type?", "correct_answer": "Mr. Spock", "incorrect_answers": ["King Billy Haraah", "The Scorpion King", "Dr. Who"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What nationality was Junko Tabei - the first woman to reach the peak of Mount Everest?", "correct_answer": "Japanese", "incorrect_answers": ["Chinese", "Indian", "Nepalese"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of Bruce Willis debut music album released in 1987?", "correct_answer": "The Return of Bruno", "incorrect_answers": ["Brave", "If It Dont Kill You, It Just Makes You Stronger", "Classic Bruce Willis: The Universal Masters Collection"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Popocat\u00e9petl, a volcano whose name means Smoking Mountain, is 70 km away from the capital of which American country?", "correct_answer": "Mexico", "incorrect_answers": ["Peru", "Canada", "Argentina"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What creature attacks Qui Gons and Obi Wans bongo in Episode 1 of Star Wars?", "correct_answer": "Giant Goober Fish", "incorrect_answers": ["Giant Snake", "Hssisi", "Sando Aqua Monster"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the name of the iris flower literally mean in Greek?", "correct_answer": "Rainbow", "incorrect_answers": ["Flower", "Sky", "Eye"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The egg of this animal contains the largest existing single cell.", "correct_answer": "Ostrich", "incorrect_answers": ["Komodo dragon", "Platypus", "Emu"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1988 Roddy Piper, Keith David and George Flower starred in this cult favorite about some special sunglasses that let you see the world as it really is.", "correct_answer": "They Live", "incorrect_answers": ["Lifeforce", "Return of the Living Dead", "Videodrome"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many Oscars did Alfred Hitchcock win for Best Director?", "correct_answer": "0", "incorrect_answers": ["4", "5", "2"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What weapon was used to shoot the crown off Rosies head in the movie Princess Protection Program?", "correct_answer": "sword", "incorrect_answers": ["knife", "shot gun", "rifle"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What traditional Chinese food is believed to improve the skin and the function of the spleen, and to promote appetite?", "correct_answer": "Bird nest", "incorrect_answers": ["Sharkfin soup", "Miso soup", "Bamboo"]}]